{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "开学",
      "answer": "Kāixué | school opens, term begins"
    },
    {
      "question": "开",
      "answer": "Kāi | to open, to start"
    },
    {
      "question": "很",
      "answer": "Hěn | very"
    },
    {
      "question": "高兴",
      "answer": "Gāoxìng | happy, pleased"
    },
    {
      "question": "高",
      "answer": "Gāo | tall"
    },
    {
      "question": "看",
      "answer": "Kàn | to watch, to look at"
    },
    {
      "question": "问",
      "answer": "Wèn | to ask"
    },
    {
      "question": "一下",
      "answer": "Yīxià | used after a verb to indicate a short, quick, random, informal action"
    },
    {
      "question": "学院",
      "answer": "Xuéyuàn | institute, college"
    },
    {
      "question": "名片",
      "answer": "Míngpiàn | business card"
    },
    {
      "question": "啊",
      "answer": "à | ah, oh"
    },
    {
      "question": "教授",
      "answer": "Jiàoshòu | professor"
    },
    {
      "question": "教",
      "answer": "Jiào | to teach, to instruct"
    }
  ]
}
